Cayce Family Collection
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
- Hugh Lynn Cayce, 1907 1982
  - Publishing, 1945 1981
    - Box 52
      - correspondence [MacMillan-McGraw Hill Company], 1970 1981; Folder 52:17
    - Box 53
      - correspondence [magazines and journals], 1963 1978; Folder 53:1
      - correspondence [Maxwell Aley Associates], 1967 1968; Folder 53:2
      - correspondence [Neville Spearman Limited], 1961 1971; Folder 53:3
      - correspondence [Pace: Piedmont Airlines Magazine], 1977 1978; Folder 53:4
      - correspondence [Paperback Library], 1966 1981; Folder 53:5
      - correspondence [Prentice-Hall], 1969 1975; Folder 53:6
      - correspondence [Psychic: The Bolen Company], 1969 1974; Folder 53:7
      - correspondence [publishers], 1964 1979; Folder 53:8
      - correspondence [publishers] international, 1963 1979; Folder 53:9
      - correspondence [Teagle and Little], 1956 1958; Folder 53:10
      - correspondence [The Outer Limits of Edgar Cayce's Power], 1969 1971; Folder 53:11
      - correspondence [translation] Edgar Cayce materials, 1962 1974; Folder 53:12
      - correspondence [William Byrd Press], 1952; Folder 53:13
      - correspondence [William Morrow and Company], 1956 1974; Folder 53:14
      - correspondence [Venture Inward], 1963 1968; Folder 53:15
    - Box 54
      - correspondence [Venture Inward], 1960 1972; Folder 54:1-54:4
      - correspondence [journal] Mind and Matter, 1957 1960; Folder 54:5
      - list of publications on Edgar Cayce with examples, 1910 1980; Folder 54:6
      - manuscript [The Woman Behind America's Best Known Psychic], undated; Folder 54:7
      - manuscript [Venture Inward], 1964; Folder 54:8
    - Box 55
      - manuscript [Venture Inward], undated; Folder 55:1
      - A.R.E. organizational charts, 1945; Folder 55:2
      - outlines [Faces of Fear], 1979 1980; Folder 55:3
      - publications [A.R.E.], undated; Folder 55:4
      - publication [essay for Truth Seekers, New York], 1954; Folder 55:5
      - publications [The Mind of Man; The Searchlight], 1952; Folder 55:6
      - workshop materials [Faces of Fear], 1980 1982; Folder 55:7
    - Box 56
      - ledger [Edgar Cayce Publishing Company], 1945 1958; Item 56:1
      - ledger supplementary materials [Edgar Cayce Publishing Company], 1945 1958; Folder 56:2
    - Box 57
      - ledger, [The Edgar Cayce Publishing Company], 1957 1959; Folder 57:1
      - ledger, [Atlantic University Dream Journal; Sundance], 1976 1978; Folder 57:2
      - ledger, [A.R.E. Press], 1962 1966; Folder 57:3
      - ledger, [A.R.E. membership], 1952 1955; Folder 57:4
      - ledger, [Edgar Cayce Foundation], 1959 1962; Folder 57:5
      - ledger, [National Bank of Commerce], 1957 1959; Folder 57:6-57:8
      - ledger, [A.R.E. memberships], 1955 1957; Folder 57:9
  - Research, 1957 1982
    - Box 58
      - magazines [MD Medical Newsmagazine], 1965 1972; Folder 58:1
      - magazine [Medical World News], 1963; Folder 58:2
    - Box 59
      - newsclippings [archaeology], 1968 1979; Folder 59:1
      - newsclippings [Association for Research and Enlightenment], 1963 1977; Folder 59:2
      - newsclippings [current events], 1968 1982; Folder 59:3
      - newsclippings [Earth Changes], 1965 1979; Folder 59:4
      - newsclippings [health], 1960 1982; Folder 59:5
    - Box 60
      - newsclippings [psychic phenomena], 1957 1980; Folder 60:1-60:2
      - newsclippings [science], 1965 1982; Folder 60:3
      - newsclippings [spirituality], 1960 1980; Folder 60:4
      - newsletter [Secretariat News: United Nations Headquarters, New York], 1980; Folder 60:5
      - photographs [archaeology and geology news], 1960 1980; Folder 60:6
      - reading extracts [health], undated; Folder 60:7
      - research notes [Essenes at Mount Carmel], 1977; Folder 60:8
      - research notes [radiocarbon dating], 1982 1987; Folder 60:9
  - Staff and Trustees, 1930 1982
    - Box 61
      - correspondence [Patricia Abrams], 1977; Folder 61:1
      - correspondence [Frank Adams], 1963 1992; Folder 61:2-61:5
      - correspondence [Robert Adriance], 1956 1966; Folder 61:6-61:9
    - Box 62
      - correspondence [Robert Adriance], 1967 2000; Folder 62:1-62:6
    - Box 63
      - correspondence [Robert Adriance] A.R.E. Library fundraiser, 1967 1968; Folder 63:1
      - correspondence [Dawn Ahart], 1980; Folder 63:2
      - correspondence [Eula Allen], 1963 1978; Folder 63:3
      - correspondence [Harold Allen], 1967 1979; Folder 63:4
      - correspondence [A.R.E. Board of Trustees], 1959 1970; Folder 63:5
      - correspondence [A.R.E. Long-Range Planning Committee], 1970 1975; Folder 63:6
      - correspondence [A.R.E. New York Center], 1958 1968; Folder 63:7-63:8
    - Box 64
      - correspondence [A.R.E. Southwest Council], 1958 1968; Folder 64:1
      - correspondence [Lester Babcoke], 1963 1982; Folder 64:2
      - correspondence [Frank Bary], 1957 1975; Folder 64:3
      - correspondence [James Allen Baraff], 1968 1975; Folder 64:4
      - correspondence [Cliff and Ursula Barker], 1969 1970; Folder 64:5
      - correspondence [Frank and Pluma Beck], 1972 1981; Folder 64:6
      - correspondence [Bruce Bickham], 1979; Folder 64:7
      - correspondence [Louis Boykin], 1970 1971; Folder 64:8
      - correspondence [Margueritte Briggs], 1961 1981; Folder 64:9
      - correspondence [Harmon Bro], 1943 1965; Folder 64:10-64:11
    - Box 65
      - correspondence [Harmon Bro], 1966 1982; Folder 65:1-65:8
    - Box 66
      - correspondence [Harmon Bro] Dream Research Project, 1971 1972; Folder 66:1
      - manuscript [Mister Cayce: An eyewitness account of a year of high adventure with a modern seer, at the end of his extraordinary life] Harmon Bro, 1980; Folder 66:2
      - correspondence [Marguerite Bro], 1969; Folder 66:3
      - correspondence [Ray Caldwell], 1976 1979; Folder 66:4
      - correspondence [Vada Carlson], 1968 1972; Folder 66:5
      - correspondence [Charles Thomas Cayce], 1977 2001; Folder 66:6
      - correspondence [Gina Cerminara], 1962 1980; Folder 66:7
      - correspondence [Elaine Chapin], 1968 1975; Folder 66:8
      - correspondence [Al Cleveland], 1965 1970; Folder 66:9
    - Box 67
      - correspondence [Jeff Coats], 1959 1978; Folder 67:1
      - correspondence [Mary Virginia Cobb], 1970 1972; Folder 67:2
      - correspondence [Joe and Dorothy Cordak], 1963 1982; Folder 67:3
      - correspondence [Juneve Damus], 1974 1982; Folder 67:4
      - correspondence [Fredrick Davidson], 1970; Folder 67:5
      - correspondence [Mildred Davis], 1935 1988; Folder 67:6
      - manuscript [New York City As I Know It] Mildred Davis, 1930; Folder 67:7
      - correspondence [Jim Dixon], 1971 1979; Folder 67:8
      - correspondence [Richard Drummond], 1973 1991; Folder 67:9-67:10
    - Box 68
      - correspondence [Jim Embleton], 1969 1970; Folder 68:1
      - correspondence [Fredrica Fields], 1977 1979; Folder 68:2
      - correspondence [Wallace Forbes], 1958 1976; Folder 68:3
      - correspondence [William Gaston], 1969 1979; Folder 68:4
      - correspondence [Lydia Schrader Gray], 1940 1942; Folder 68:4a
      - correspondence [Harvey Green], 1980 1982; Folder 68:5
      - correspondence [Ray and Rebecca Hanchey], 1963 1971; Folder 68:6-68:7
      - correspondence [Robert Hardy], 1985 2012; Folder 68:8
      - correspondence [Harvey Humann], 1970 1981; Folder 68:9
      - correspondence [Edward Jamail], 1973 1981; Folder 68:10
      - correspondence [Anna and Robert Jeffries], 1967 1974; Folder 68:11-68:12
    - Box 69
      - correspondence [Robert Jeffries], 1975 1982; Folder 69:1
      - correspondence [Erik and Lorraine Jensen], 1978 1982; Folder 69:2
      - correspondence [Rudolph Johnson], 1964 1981; Folder 69:3-69:4
      - correspondence [David Kahn], 1944 1969; Folder 69:5
      - correspondence [Alton Ketchum], 1968; Folder 69:6
      - correspondence [Worth Kidd], 1967 1979; Folder 69:7
    - Box 70
      - correspondence [Noel Langley], 1960 1976; Folder 70:1
      - correspondence [David Leary], 1973 2008; Folder 70:2
      - correspondence [Norrene Leary], 1975 1982; Folder 70:3
      - correspondence [staff and trustees] M, 1961 1982; Folder 70:4-70:5
      - correspondence [Murray Main], 1963 1979; Folder 70:6
      - correspondence [Gerald Matlin], 1977 1981; Folder 70:7
      - correspondence [Ted Matthews], 1976; Folder 70:8
      - correspondence[ McArthur Committee], 1977 1982; Folder 70:9
      - correspondence [Thomas McCaleb], 1968 1969; Folder 70:10
    - Box 71
      - correspondence [Thomas McCaleb], 1968 1974; Folder 71:1-71:4
      - correspondence [Robert McGarey], 1969 1976; Folder 71:5
      - correspondence [William McGarey], 1961 1970; Folder 71:6-71:7
      - correspondence [Ruben Miller], 1968 1985; Folder 71:8
    - Box 72
      - correspondence [Shane Miller], 1962 1993; Folder 72:1
      - correspondence [Frank Mitchell], 1961 1979; Folder 72:2
      - correspondence [William Frazer Morris], 1968 1971; Folder 72:3
      - correspondence [Rufus and Sam Mosely], 1974 1982; Folder 72:4
      - correspondence [Eugene and Mary Mueller], 1971 1975; Folder 72:5
      - correspondence [Ann and Arch Ogden], 1961 1980; Folder 72:6-72:7
      - correspondence [Dorothy Olson], 1974; Folder 72:8
      - correspondence [Walter Pahnke], 1961 1971; Folder 72:9
      - correspondence [Ernest F. Pecci], 1969 1975; Folder 72:10
      - correspondence [Paul Perkins], 1969 1972; Folder 72:11
      - correspondence [Herbert Puryear], 1963 1974; Folder 72:12
      - correspondence [Meredith Puryear], 1968 1980; Folder 72:13
      - correspondence [Harold Reilly], 1965 1971; Folder 72:14
    - Box 73
      - correspondence [Harold Reilly], 1972 1982; Folder 73:1
      - correspondence [Linda Quest], 1975 1979; Folder 73:2
      - correspondence [E. Glenn Sanderfur], 1977 1981; Folder 73:3
      - correspondence [Dennie Sanders], 1981 1982; Folder 73:4
      - correspondence [James Saxild], 1974 1975; Folder 73:5
      - correspondence [Ann and Bernard Schreiner], 1966 1980; Folder 73:6
      - correspondence [Stephan Schwartz], 1967 1980; Folder 73:7-73:8
      - correspondence [Stephan Schwartz] The Talking Idol Project, 1978; Folder 73:9
      - correspondence [Elsie Sechrist], 1972 1976; Folder 73:10
    - Box 74
      - correspondence [Elsie Sechrist], 1969 1982; Folder 74:1-74:3
      - correspondence [Wilfred and Elsie Sechrist], 1954 1968; Folder 74:4-74:6
      - correspondence [Millie Shaw], 1970 1980; Folder 74:7
      - correspondence [Violet Shelley], 1968 1976; Folder 74:8
      - correspondence [Beverly and Riley Simmons], 1971 1974; Folder 74:9
    - Box 75
      - correspondence [Bruce and Jane Smith], 1972 1982; Folder 75:1
      - correspondence [Bob Smock], 1972 1974; Folder 75:2
      - correspondence [Jess Stearn], 1961 1982; Folder 75:3-75:6
      - correspondence [Florence Sterba], 1973 1976; Folder 75:7
      - correspondence [Ariel Taylor], 1961 1962; Folder 75:8
      - correspondence [William Thetford], 1970 1977; Folder 75:9
      - correspondence [Mark Thurston], 1968 1981; Folder 75:10
      - correspondence [Kevin Todeschi], 1980 1982; Folder 75:11
      - correspondence [Gladys Davis Turner], 1973 1982; Folder 75:12-75:13
      - correspondence [John Van Auken], 1971; Folder 75:14
    - Box 76
      - correspondence [Katherine Whitman], 1954 1955; Folder 76:1
      - correspondence [James Windsor], 1963 1981; Folder 76:2
      - correspondence [Shirley Winston], 1964 1977; Folder 76:3
      - memoranda [A.R.E. Publishing Company and Foundation staff], 1959; Folder 76:4
      - newsletter [Staff News], 1959 1960; Folder 76:5
    - Box 77
      - correspondence [A.R.E. contacts in Germany], 1960 1982; Folder 77:1
      - correspondence [A.R.E. contacts in Great Britain and Ireland], 1969 1979; Folder 77:2
      - correspondence [A.R.E. contacts in Israel], 1964 1978; Folder 77:3
      - correspondence [A.R.E. contacts in Mexico], 1970 1971; Folder 77:4
      - correspondence [A.R.E. contacts in the Netherlands], 1969 1981; Folder 77:5
      - correspondence [A.R.E. contacts in South America], 1972 1977; Folder 77:6
      - correspondence [A.R.E. contacts in Tibet], 1969 1975; Folder 77:7
      - correspondence [H.N. Banerjee], 1963 1970; Folder 77:8
      - correspondence [Jogdish Chandra], 1969 1972; Folder 77:9
      - correspondence [charter] A.R.E. Germany, 1981 1982; Folder 77:10
      - correspondence [Victor Chua], 1977 1982; Folder 77:11
      - correspondence [Albert Doss] Egypt Project, 1974 1982; Folder 77:12
    - Box 78
      - correspondence [Lawrence Follas], 1969 1979; Folder 78:1
      - correspondence [Horst Goede], 1978 1982; Folder 78:2
      - correspondence [hypnosis], 1956 1981; Folder 78:3-78:6
      - correspondence [Iran Project and trips], 1973 1978; Folder 78:7
      - correspondence [Israel trip], 1966; Folder 78:8
    - Box 79
      - correspondence [John Philip Law], 1975; Folder 79:1
      - correspondence [Dr. Cyrus Lee], 1981 1982; Folder 79:2
      - correspondence [Razee Moazami] Iran trip, 1973 1981; Folder 79:3
      - correspondence [Mount Carmel, Israel archaeological project], 1977; Folder 79:4
      - correspondence [Joe and Phyllis Olsen] Iran trip, 1972 1981; Folder 79:5
      - correspondence [I.C. Sharma], 1968 1981; Folder 79:6
      - correspondence [Millie Shaw], 1974; Folder 79:7
      - correspondence [Egerton Sykes], 1965 1980; Folder 79:8
    - Box 80
      - correspondence [professional], 1945 1981; Folder 80:1-80:2
      - correspondence [David Zink] Bimini, 1974 1984; Folder 80:3
      - notes [college student past life project], 1947; Folder 80:4
      - photographs [correspondence], 1960 1981; Folder 80:5
      - publications [pamphlets], 1963 1973; Folder 80:6
      - publications [A.R.E. programs], 1968 1970; Folder 80:7
      - publications [hypnosis], 1963; Folder 80:8
      - reading [Neva Dell Hunter], 1957; Folder 80:9
      - research materials [Essenes at Mount Carmel], 1965 1977; Folder 80:10
      - travel materials [Iran trip], 1973 1975; Folder 80:11
- Edgar Evans Cayce, 1950 2013
  - Box 81
    - certificates and diplomas, 1935 1989; Folder 81:1
    - charter [Edgar Cayce Foundation], 1948 1973; Folder 81:2
    - correspondence [film contracts], 1975 1991; Folder 81:3
    - correspondence [personal], 1957 2009; Folder 81:4
    - correspondence [professional], 1955 2008; Folder 81:5
    - correspondence [publishing], 1989 1990; Folder 81:6
    - film contract [Clear Window Productions], 1991; Folder 81:7
    - film contract [Henry Gellis and Jess Stearn], 1976 1983; Folder 81:8
    - film contract [Paramount Pictures Corporation], 1956; Folder 81:9
    - identification cards, 1939 2013; Folder 81:10
    - lecture notes, undated; Folder 81:11
    - marriage certificate [Edgar Evans Cayce and Kathryn Bane], 1942; Folder 81:12
    - memorial card [Edgar Evans Cayce], 2013; Folder 81:13
    - newsclippings [Edgar Cayce], 1910 2006; Folder 81:14
    - newsclippings [education], 1935 2009; Folder 81:15
    - newsclippings [speaking engagements], 1971; Folder 81:16
    - notes [humor], undated; Folder 81:17
    - pamphlets [historical], 1960 2006; Folder 81:18
    - publications [A.R.E.], 1945 2011; Folder 81:19
    - proposal [Requesting Permission to Pursue Geological Studies in the Giza Plateau Area] Robert M. Schoch; M.G. Barakat, 1991; Folder 81:20
    - publishing materials [Atlantis Revisited], 2006; Folder 81:21
    - report card [Oceana High School], 1934; Folder 81:22
    - reports [archaeology] Atlantis and Egypt, 1970 2003; Folder 81:23
    - reports [health readings], 1960; Folder 81:24
  - Box 82
    - book contract [The Mysteries of Atlantis], 1987; Folder 82:1
    - book contracts [The Mysteries of Atlantis Revisited], 1994 2005; Folder 82:2
    - correspondence [audiobook] The Mysteries of Atlantis, 1988; Folder 82:3
    - correspondence [Bill Donato] Atlantis, 1997; Folder 82:4
    - correspondence [book contracts] Mysteries of Atlantis Revisited, 1987 2006; Folder 82:5
    - correspondence [film contracts] Mysteries of Atlantis Revisited, 1994 1999; Folder 82:6
    - index [M. Peterson's Atlantis index], undated; Folder 82:7
    - newsclippings [Atlantis], 1968 2005; Folder 82:8-82:9
    - research materials [Atlantis], 1976 2005; Folder 82:10
  - Box 83
    - research material [Atlantis], 1970 2005; Folder 83:1-83:5
    - revisions [Mysteries of Atlantis Revisited], 2006; Folder 83:6
    - royalties [St. Martin's Press], 1998 2006; Folder 83:7
  - Box 84
    - correspondence [Humor from the Psychic], 1978 2006; Folder 84:1
    - correspondence [The Outer Limits of Edgar Cayce's Power], 1970 2007; Folder 84:2-84:3
    - draft [The Outer Limits of Edgar Cayce's Power], undated; Folder 84:4
    - manuscript [Humor from the Psychic], 1978; Folder 84:5
    - manuscript and supplementary materials [Two Electrical Appliances Described in the Edgar Cayce Readings], 1965 2007; Folder 84:6
  - Box 85
    - agreement [Edgar Evans Cayce, Hugh Lynn Cayce, John William Prince], 1953; Folder 85:1
    - correspondence [A.R.E. Press and Paraview] Treasure Hunting with a Psychic, 1997 2003; Folder 85:2
    - manuscript [Treasure Hunting with a Psychic], undated; Folder 85:3-85:7
    - reading extracts [3812], 1931; Folder 85:8
  - Box 86
    - manuscript [Thoran of Thrace], 1950 1960; Folder 86:1-86:2
    - maps [Atlantis research], undated; Folder 86:3
    - map [Cape Henry, Virginia], 1948; Folder 86:4
    - pamphlets [Radioactive and Wet Cell appliances], 1964 1995; Folder 86:5
    - publications [U.S. Geological Survey], 1994 2001; Folder 86:6
    - report [The Discovery and Possible Significance of X-Kukican, Ancient Mayan site] Alabama Museum of Natural History, 1965; Folder 86:7
    - desk name plate, undated; Item 86:8
    - cartographic tool, undated; Item 86:9
    - watch face (2), undated; Item 86:10-86:11
  - Box 87
    - recording [Edgar Evans Cayce lecture: Mysteries of Atlantis: 1999 Gulf Breeze UFO Conference], Item 87:1
    - recording [Edgar Evans Cayce: The Mysteries of Atlantis Revealed, 21st Century Radio's Dr. Bob Hieronymus Show ], 1989; Item 87:2
    - recording [Art Bell and Edgar Evans Cayce], 1998; Item 87:3
    - recording [The Story of Edgar Cayce], undated; Item 87:4
    - recording [Beyond Reason: Edgar Evans Cayce on his Father's Readings of Atlantis], undated; Item 87:5
    - recording [Message to Mr. Edgar Evans Cayce from KNRY 1240], 1998; Item 87:6
    - recording [21st Century Radio's Hieronimus and Co. American Radio Networks: October Surprise: Hostages for Arms Deal], 1990; Item 87:7
    - recording [21st Century Radio's Hieronimus and Co.: Edgar Evans Cayce: Plato's Theory on Atlantis], 1992; Item 87:8
    - recording [21st Century Radio's Hieronimus and Co., Edgar Evans Cayce: Mystery of Atlantis], 1997; Item 87:9
    - recording [Hieronimus and Co.'s 21st Century Radio, Edgar Evans Cayce: Mysteries of Atlantis], 1999; Item 87:10
    - recording [Edgar Evans Cayce on Shine: Talk Radio With Spirit], 2001; Item 87:11
    - recording [The Story of Atlantis], undated; Item 87:12
    - book, [Plane Trigonometry: A Textbook for Schools and Colleges], 1928; Item 87:13
    - book, [The Nature of the World and Man], 1926; Item 87:14
    - book, [Principles of Electrical Engineering], 1930; Item 87:15
    - book, [The Elements of Geometry], 1894; Item 87:16
  - Box 88
    - photographs [Edgar, Gertrude, Hugh Lynn, and Edgar Evans Cayce], 1920 1941; Folder 88:1
    - photographs [Edgar Evans Cayce], 1937 2000; Folder 88:2
    - photographs [Edgar Evans and Kathryn Bane Cayce and family], 1942 1970; Folder 88:3
    - photograph, framed [Edgar Evans and Kathryn Bane Cayce], 2002; Folder 88:4
    - slide tray [Walt Disney World collectible slides], 1971 1972; Item 88:5
    - slide tray [family photographs], 1972 1975; Item 88:6
    - slide carousel, 1970 1980; Item 88:7
  - Box 89
    - slide tray [photographs of Oceana and Virginia Beach], 1970 1980; Item 89:1
    - slide tray [photographs of Sandra's visit; Bobbie's wedding; Beanie's farm], 1970 1980; Item 89:2
    - slide carousel [family photographs], 1970 1980; Item 89:3
    - slide carousel [Kat and Edgar trip to Phoenix 1970 / Columbus], Item 89:4
  - Box 90
    - recording [Atlantis: A Legend Resurfaces], 1999; Item 90:1
    - recording [Edgar Evans Cayce Exclusive: Prophecies of Edgar Cayce; 1999 Gulf Breeze UFO Conference], Item 90:2
    - recording [Century #105: Religion], 2001; Item 90:3
    - recording [Channel 10: In Search of Atlantis], 1996; Item 90:4
    - recording [Unsolved Mysteries: Edgar Cayce / Sphinx Project: John Anthony West], 1991; Item 90:5
    - recording [interview, [Edgar Evans Cayce], undated; Item 90:6
    - recording [Mysterious Worlds: Edgar Evans Cayce], undated; Item 90:7
    - recording [Unsolved Mysteries: Edgar Cayce], 1991; Item 90:8
    - recording [Ancient Prophecies], undated; Item 90:9
    - recording [Encounters: Cayce; Earthquakes; Friendship with Russia], 1994; Item 90:10
    - recording [Edgar Cayce and His Legacy], 1988; Item 90:11
    - recording [Biography: Edgar Cayce, The Sleeping Psychic], 1997; Item 90:12
    - recording [Edgar Evans Cayce lecture: Mysteries of Atlantis; 1999 Gulf Breeze UFO Conference], Item 90:13
    - recording [Decoding the Past: The Other Nostradamus], 2005; Item 90:14
    - recording [Rudolph Gautenbrink's Robot Finds a Door in the Great Pyramid / John Anthony West and Robert Schoch on the Age of the Sphinx], undated; Item 90:15
    - recording [The Technologies of the Gods], 1998; Item 90:16
- Charles Thomas Cayce, 1984 1990
  - Box 91
    - conference materials [Relationships: Stumbling Blocks to Stepping Stones] Charles Thomas Cayce; Leslie Goodman Cayce, 1990; Folder 91:1
    - conference materials [Spiritual Principles in Business], 1984 1987; Folder 91:2
    - correspondence [John D. Beahrs], 1990; Folder 91:3
    - correspondence [Rivka Bertisch], 1989; Folder 91:4
    - correspondence [Bio-Electro Magnetics Institute], 1989; Folder 91:5
    - correspondence [Bennett G. Braun], 1989; Folder 91:6
    - lecture notes [Meditation and Visualization], 1990; Folder 91:7
    - lecture notes [Reincarnation], 1990; Folder 91:8
    - lecture notes [Self-Analysis: Setting the Ideal], 1990; Folder 91:9
    - lecture notes [Times of Change: Holistic Living], 1989; Folder 91:10
    - magazine [Psychic Guide], 1989; Folder 91:11
    - newsletter [Brain Mind Bulletin], 1988; Folder 91:12